killstar.com 2019-05-06

# PRIVACY POLICY | KILLSTAR - UK Store

**What is this Privacy Policy for?**

This privacy policy is for this website [www.KILLSTAR.com](http://www.killstar.com/) and served by DRACO DISTRIBUTION LTD and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.

The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.

**The Website**

This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all International & EU laws and General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) requirements for user privacy.

**Use of Cookies**

This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. A cookie is a small amount of data, which may include a unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. We assign a different cookie to each device that accesses our website. This website uses a cookie control system allowing the user to the website to confirm the use of cookies on their computer / device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user's computer / device.

Cookies are small files saved to the user's computers hard drive that track, save and store information about the user's interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.

This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage (you can red Google’s privacy policy at the following link : https://policies.google.com/privacy). The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. Cookies are used for shopping cart fulfilment and abandoned cart engagement. Cookies can be disabled through your web browsing software.

Other cookies may be stored to your computers hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected. We work with a number of 3rd party services to ensure your shopping experience on Killstar.com is optimal. All relevant 3rd parties have their own privacy policies that are compliant with GDPR. All requests regarding our privacy policy and personal information stored should be directed to [privacy@killstar.com](mailto:privacy@killstar.com) .

**Contact & Communication**

Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own consent. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998 and subsequent General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process.

This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products / services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Or whereby you the consumer has previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to. This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material. We do not share our mailing list with any third parties.

**Retention of Personal Information**

In general, we keep your personal information throughout your relationship with us. We may retain archived copies of your personal information for legitimate business purposes such as monitoring refunds, and to comply with the law. For our customers this means we will keep your information until you exercise your ‘right to be forgotten’.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

We work with a variety of 3rd parties and service providers to help provide you with our services & we may share personal information with them to support these efforts. We may also share your personal information under the following circumstances:

  * To prevent, investigate, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of a person, violations of our Terms of Service (<https://www.killstar.com/pages/ts-cs>), or as otherwise required by the law.
  * To respond to legal requirements, or to respond to lawful court orders, subpoenas, warrants, or other requests by public authorities.
  * Personal information may also be shared with a company that acquires our business, whether through merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganisation, or other similar transaction or proceeding. If this happens, we will post a notice on our website.

What we don’t do with your personal information – we do not and never will share, disclose, sell ,rent, or otherwise provide personal information to other companies (other than within the tight parameters specified above) for the marketing of their own products or services.

**Email Newsletter**

This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about products and services supplied by this website. Users can subscribe through an online process should they wish to do so which has a double opt-in process in place to deter any unauthorised signups. Some subscriptions may be manually processed through prior written agreement with the user, such an influencers and users who encounter an error at sign-up. Our mailing list is managed through a 3rd party vendor, MailChimp, who comply with all required legislation.

All personal details relating to subscriptions are held securely and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). No personal details are passed on to third parties nor shared with companies / people outside of the company that operates this website. Under the Data Protection Act 1998 and GDPR, you may request a copy of personal information held about you by this website's email newsletter program. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the business address at the bottom of this policy or email us via [privacy@killstar.com](mailto:privacy@killstar.com) .

Email marketing campaigns published by this website or its owners may contain tracking facilities within the actual email. Subscriber activity is tracked and stored in a database for future analysis and evaluation. Such tracked activity may include; the opening of emails, forwarding of emails, the clicking of links within the email content, times, dates and frequency of activity [this is by no far a comprehensive list].  
This information is used to refine future email campaigns and supply the user with more relevant content based around their activity.

In compliance with GDPR subscribers are given the opportunity to un-subscribe or amend their subscription preferences at any time through an automated system. This process is detailed at the footer of each email campaign.

**Review Invitations**

We have partnered with Trustpilot to collect verified customer service reviews. Customers will receive an email invitation 14-days after placing their order (plus a reminder 7-days later if a review has not been left before then) asking for a review. There is no obligation to respond although we welcome all customer feedback.

**External Links**

Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised to adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website. (External links are clickable text / banner / image links to other websites).

The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

**Social Media Platforms**

Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as email or social media.

This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

**Shortened Links in Social Media**

This website and its owners through their social media platform accounts may share web links to relevant web pages. Some are shortened URLs [web addresses]. Users are advised to take caution and good judgement before clicking any shortened URLs published on social media platforms by this website and its owners. Despite the best efforts to ensure only genuine URLs are published many social media platforms are prone to spam and hacking and therefore this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any shortened links.

Policy last updated 25th February 2019.

If you have any questions about privacy please contact us by email at privacy@killstar.com or via mail:

DRACO DISTRIBUTION LTD  
Unit 9 Boundary Road  
Rutherglen  
Glasgow G73 1DB  
United Kingdom
